<resources>
    <string-array name="language_entries">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Spanish</item>
        <item>French</item>
        <item>Chinese</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="language_values">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>es</item>
        <item>fr</item>
        <item>zh-CN</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="proficiency_entries">
        <item>Beginner</item>
        <item>Intermediate</item>
        <item>Advanced</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="proficiency_values">
        <item>Beginner</item>
        <item>Intermediate</item>
        <item>Advanced</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="language_tips">
        <item>
            Immerse yourself in English media such as movies, TV shows, podcasts, and books.
            This not only exposes you to authentic language use but also helps improve your
            listening skills, pronunciation, and overall comprehension.
        </item>
        <item>
            When using quizzes for language learning, vary question types to cover multiple skills.
            Review both correct and incorrect answers to reinforce learning. Create quizzes at
            different difficulty levels for continuous challenge and growth.
        </item>
        <item>
            When using flashcards for language learning, strive for active engagement rather than
            passive memorization. Review regularly and focus on the words or phrases that prove more
            challenging,ensuring a comprehensive grasp of the language.
        </item>
        <item>
            Don\'t forget to track your progress today! Check out our Progress section to see how
            far you\'ve come in your language learning journey. It\'s a great way to stay motivated
            and celebrate your achievements!
        </item>
        <item>
            Expand your learning horizons today! Visit our resource page for more information about
            our app. FluentU is a treasure trove waiting to enhance your language learning journey!
        </item>
        <item>
            Define achievable language learning goals by specifying weekly targets for learning new words and
            practicing specific conversation topics. Ensure these goals are realistic and trackable,
            and adapt them as you progress in your language learning journey.
        </item>
        <item>
            When using flashcards, tap to translate the text and use the text-to-speech feature for
            active listening. Enhance your pronunciation and comprehension by hearing the words aloud
        </item>
        <item>
            Consistent daily practice across speaking, listening, reading, and writing is crucial
            for language improvement. Allocate a short time each day to work on these key skills
            in your target language.
        </item>
        <item>
            Personalize your profile with accurate details and a clear picture to enhance your user
            experience. Providing genuine information helps create a more engaging and tailored
            experience within the app.
        </item>
        <item>
            Embrace the learning process—mistakes are milestones on your language journey.
            Stay patient and persistent in your pursuit of fluency.
        </item>
        <!-- Add more tips as needed -->
    </string-array>
</resources>